Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
a Sony Company
Hi. My name is Peter Parker.
You don't remember me.
but I have something to tell you...
that's gonna sound crazy.
But it's the truth.
And I know you're gonna believe me...
because you're very good at telling when I'm lying.
E.V.. can you check the calibration of my targeting matrix?
That doesn't feel zeroed in to me.
Checking target calibration.
Hey. E.V.. take five.
Standing by.
We used to know each other.
We were together.
But something bad was gonna happen...
and the only way to stop it was to make everyone forget me.
First day at MIT. let's go!
My gosh! We're here! We made it!
MJ. come on.
Including you.
Pretend like you're not the happiest you've ever been...
in your entire life right now.
I can't.
-Let's just do this! You're happy!
-Okay. okay. okay. Okay.
Because I'm not just Peter Parker.
I'm Spider-Man.
I'm really. really understanding the culture out here in Boston is just so different.
And sometimes Spider-Man has to do the hard thing...
even if it breaks Peter Parker's heart.
And everyone here is like.
"Pahk the cah by the hahba.
And maybe that's my responsibility.
To live alone with the truth.
But the truth is. MJ. that I love you.
And I hope that deep down...
something inside of you remembers that you love me. too.
Suspect is 5'8". 5'10". medium build.
But until then. I'm just gonna be Spider-Man.
Incoming!
Hey. get him!
Hey. hey. hey. Whoa. whoa. whoa!
Members of the Manfredi crime syndicate...
were apprehended by Spider-Man yesterday.
Hey. we live on the same floor.
Cool.
Does anybody ever come up here?
Not unless they like asbestos.
We've just been using it for storage.
It's perfect.
Hey. everyone. sophomore-year-Ned is back.
Older. wiser. flyer.
Let's go!
-What is on your face?
-How do you feel about it?
I mean. you look like an assistant coach.
You sure you wanna do this. Scorpion?
Did you miss me. Spidey?
If I drop you from here...
how long you think
it will take you to hit the ground?
Well. I don't know. You tell me.
Let's end this on a high note?
Yo. Lonnie!
Wha ha happened?
DeWolff. all the evidence you're gonna need is in the trunk of his car.
You tryin' to take my job. Spider-Man?
Hey. you guys are the professionals.
I'm just a volunteer.
It's a new New York.
Thanks to Spider-Man.
crime rates have dropped to a record low.
Police and Damage Control give much of the credit...
to the masked hero.
Initiate HUD test.
Armed robbery at Civic Union Bank.
In the past six months.
he has taken down...
every major crime lord across the five boroughs...
including the superpowered ninja group The Hand.
A Worker Survives Near-Fatal Oil Rig Emergency
He is the pride of New York City.
The hero every grown-up relies on and every kid wants to be.
Final semester. MIT.
My gosh. we're graduating in a month.
We've made so many memories.
Where do I begin?
Night swimming in the Charles River with Jim and Wiley.
The infamous food fun at the Banana Lounge.
Pulling all-nighters in Stud 5 with MJ and Nate Dawg.
It feels like yesterday
I was sitting on a roof with MJ...
dreaming about coming here together.
and I still can't believe we did it.
I'm so grateful for all the friends that I've made.
I couldn't imagine going through this with anyone else.
Ned. who do you think is actually watching these?
-I don't know. But maybe someone.
-Okay.
Okay. well. bye. someone.
-What? No!
-Bye. We're done. Yeah. we're done.
Lasciare davanti alla porta
-Parliamo del centro di Brooklyn
-in pieno giorno.
Un colpo cosi. lo sai che c'entra Foswell.
High profile job like that.
you know that Foswell was involved.
Yeah. I hear you. but can you prove it?
Yeah. I'm going through his financial records...
and I'm following his crew every night.
Do you do anything besides work?
You know the saying.
"You do something you love...
you don't work a day in your life.
-Mom. where's my calculator?
-I don't know.
Trust me. aight?
Being married to the job never ends well.
Well. don't worry about it. I'll be okay.
Yeah?
You still getting them headaches. though?
Yeah. But I'll be fine.
I don't know. man.
I think you're body's tryin' to tell you somethin'.
Like you need to get outta that suit every once in a while.
Mom. do you know where my calculator is?
I don't know. Papi.
What you need is some real human connection.
What? And we're not connecting?
Nah. dude. I don't know your name.
your face. or nothing about you.
I don't think you've ever asked me a question about my life.
Sure. I have.
Yeah. what are my kids' names?
Well. for starters. your son's name's Papi.
Is it Spider-Man?
I can't tell you that. sweetheart.
That means it's Spider-Man.
Gosh.
A hijacked tank is heading southbound past 34th Street.
All available units respond.
Hey. you getting this?
More work. Lucky you.
Okay. I'll see you out there.
I'm so sorry. I gotta go.
I got you. Spidey!
No. no. I don't need your...
Hey! Heads up!
You okay. kid? Yeah. you're okay.
See ya later.
You wouldn't know it just by looking at it...
but this very street was completely destroyed in the Battle of New York.
Come on. come on. come on.
Come on.
God.
Hey.
The hell. Frank?
You just hit me with the van!
Quit your whimpering.
We're not doing that again. Frank.
You're goddamn right we're not.
This time you're gonna get the hell outta my way.
You mean. instead of saving your life?
You gonna talk about that Staten Island bullshit again?
Well. you said it. not me.
Jeez.
Look. man. you can't just shoot yourself out of every situation.
Innocent people get hurt.
Who do you think's downrange of that tank. dumb-dumb?
Suit yourself.
Jackass.
This freakin' guy.
Go home. Frank!
I'm gonna kill this kid.
-DeWolff?
-Are you gonna stop that thing or what?
It's heading straight for the Damage Control Detention Center.
I'm trying.
Try harder.
There's a lot of scary dudes locked up in there.
Well. who do you think put them in there?
Let's go. Scorpion. Moving day.
All right. everybody. clear out!
This guy is armed and dangerous.
Get out of the vehicle. ma'am.
I was thinking the same thing.
Spider-Man?
Where am I?
What?
Move! Move! Move!
Keep her for questioning.
Clear the building.
Enjoy the ride. Scorpion!
You won't be seeing much daylight in supermax.
Scorpions are nocturnal. buddy.
The building is under attack.
Get the prisoner out of here now!
Sir!
You gotta take off now!
The building has been breached. Go! Go!
Hey. fire it up! Go! Go!
Change of plans!
Take him to the helipad at Bellevue.
-What?
-That's an order from Director Metzger. Go!
Now!
Copy that.
Hey! What...
How did I get up here?
Spider-Man. save me. would you?
Who are you?
You can see me.
Tell me who you are.
You first.
Hey. Hey.
You pushed me out.
Interesting.
What the hell was that?
Did you just try to jump into my mind?
You know. the whole time you've been chasing me...
you forgot to ask yourself a very important question.
What's in the tank?
Go! Move.
Spider-Man?
What just happened?
I don't know.
Hey. good job.
Hey. way to go. Spidey.
You guys okay? You good?
I swear. All the things they said I did.
I don't remember doing any of them.
It's okay. it's okay.
Look. let these people take good care of you.
I would never hurt you.
-Okay.
-I love you. Spider-Man.
Yeah. All right. buddy. All right.
-Hey. what do you got?
-Here. get this.
Chopper took Scorpion to Bellevue.
Ten minutes later.
a guard walked him right out the door.
What?
What about the tank?
Stolen from the Damage Control warehouse in Brooklyn.
Driver was a janitor who worked there.
You got a motive?
Nada.
And no criminal record.
Scorpion must've gotten to her somehow.
Yeah. Maybe.
What do you mean. "maybe"?
I mean. I don't know.
But I know someone that might.
Where you going?
You keep following the leads on Scorpion.
I'm gonna go talk to someone.
Hi. is this 3250 Brighton Beach?
Okay.
I think I know what that means.
Take off your clothes.
What?
You don't wear clothes in the banya.
Ditch the leotard.
This is not a leotard.
Your text said that this was your office.
This is my office.
Get in.
I'm fine. thanks. I'll just...
My office. my rules.
This way you get to enjoy a nice. relaxing soak...
and I get to see that
you don't have any weapons...
and we both win.
Okay.
Really? What. you never take that off?
No. I... You know. it defeats the whole anonymous thing.
Even for your girlfriend or boyfriend or whatever?
There's a lot of conjecture online.
And super graphic artwork. Have you seen?
The one with you and the ten Mysterios. it's...
I've seen it. I've...
It's hard to unsee. to be honest.
But. look. I don't have anyone.
I just kinda keep to myself.
All by yourself? All the time?
No wonder you're so sad.
-I'm not so sad.
-A little bit.
Could we just talk about what I came here to talk to you about...
the attack on Damage Control?
Yes. So. that is more your area.
Like. small potato stuff.
Whereas the New Avengers are focusing on big potato stuff.
Right. okay. Well. there's more to it than that. you know...
the driver and the others who were helping...
it was like someone was talking to me through them.
Like someone was looking at me through their eyes.
And you're wondering if it's mind control?
-Exactly.
-Like how they used on me in the Red Room?
-And the other widows?
-Right.
-Right. No. I don't think so.
I actually think it's probably more like possession.
Possession?
Like a ghost or a demon.
- Man.
- Or in Russia. we have leshy.
Leshy rules the forest and can possess...
Sorry.
Whatever it is.
they are looking for something.
This is the fourth attack on the Damage Control facility this month.
And what do you think they're looking for?
I don't know.
But you know what?
After the attack today...
there was a cross-agency cyber security alert that got triggered.
Someone accessed the Damage Control restricted servers...
using credentials from 30 employees from the way station.
They all searched for the same thing.
V-Max.
Well. what does that mean?
I mean. it could be alien tech...
or secretive weapon programs...
or launch codes or...
I don't know. this is for you to figure out.
-This is small. baby potato stuff...
-Okay. okay.
-...not big potato brain stuff.
-You don't have to shout about it. Jeez.
Maybe I'll just go ask Damage Control myself.
You know. you're not completely anonymous anymore.
I've seen your belly button.
-Okay.
-Bye.
God.
Hi. I got an appointment with...
Director Metzger. Yes.
Please step through the scanner.
Enhanced human detected.
Superior strength.
Superior agility.
Heightened senses.
Exogenous DNA. Arachnid.
Please remove your face covering for identity scan.
No. I can't do that.
-That's not possible.
-Failure to remove your face covering...
will result in defensive measures.
Defensive measures? What are you talk...
Guys. guys. guys!
I can't take my mask off. I'm...
Spider-Man.
He's all right. At ease.
My apologies.
We are so glad you're here.
Bill Metzger. Director of Damage Control.
How are you?
I'm good. thank you.
We had to beef up security around here.
but I hope we didn't give you a fright.
-No. not at all.
-All right. come on. This way.
This floor is mostly research and administrative.
Downstairs. we have incident cleanup. laboratories. agent training.
-Hey. what are they doing here?
-It's okay.
The Hand works for us now.
After you brought them in. I realized that...
fundamentally. they're a group of kids without a leader.
All they needed was a little direction.
Then. suddenly.
all the things that made them dangerous...
turned them into an invaluable part of our security team.
You can look at the many threats that face us and see only danger.
Or you can see opportunity.
Okay.
Wow. look at that.
In the hands of Shocker.
these are a nuisance.
But it doesn't mean we can't learn from the technology...
or respect the innovation.
Our mission is to redirect destructive energy into something useful.
That's the true meaning of Damage Control.
Be careful with that.
Right this way.
I wanted to talk to you about the recent attacks on the agency.
There's been four. right?
Please have a seat.
You are right.
It appears we're faced with a threat we can't control.
One we can't even see.
But you can.
I saw the security footage.
I also read Detective DeWolff's report.
I believe you understand exactly what we're up against.
Someone or something that can hop into people's minds.
But not yours.
No. I mean. it tried. but it couldn't.
I'm gonna be honest with you.
We're on our heels right now.
God forbid if it were to get in here and find whatever it is it's looking for...
the consequences could be unimaginable.
Well. let me guess. is whatever it's looking for in that giant vault?
There are some things.
because of the nature of my job...
I cannot tell you.
But I believe you are our best defense against this.
You're the only one who can sense it.
You're the only one who's immune to it.
I'm counting on you to defeat it.
That's a pretty good speech. Director.
I'll do everything that I can. I promise.
Well. then consider yourself a friend of Damage Control.
Thank you.
I'll be in touch.
I wanted to ask...
the phrase "V-Max"
doesn't mean anything to you. does it?
No. Where'd you hear that?
It's just. you know.
nature of being a superhero...
there are some things I just can't tell ya.
Anyway. I'll see you later.
You guys are doing great. Keep it up.
I don't think Metzger knows any more than we do...
but I told him I'd do whatever I can to help.
You wanna help?
The best thing you could do...
is find Scorpion.
He's our only lead.
Yeah. I know. I have every camera in the city running a facial recognition scan for him.
That sounds super illegal. Spider-Man.
I'mma pretend I didn't hear that.
Yeah. probably for the best.
But look. if he shows his face. we'll know.
Do you have any mini-kegs?
Down at the end.
Thanks.
I'll call you back.
Easy.
Hey. also. you got any Sharkfire Energy?
Yeah.
No. no. no.
I don't want any. That stuff will kill you.
You know. all my friends were drinking them during finals...
and now they're addicted.
and so I'm gonna need you to not sell me any.
Memorize my face.
Please do not sell this guy any Sharkfire.
Sure. Whatever.
Actually. I'll take one.
Last one.
Maybe two.
And then never sell me any.
Damn it.
Yo. Ned!
-What?
-Ned!
-Give me that.
-My guy. appreciate you.
-Let's go!
-Yeah. man.
-Yeah! What time did y'all get here?
We came here. like. half an hour ago.
You need a drink.
Take this. take this. take it.
Thanks.
See you've stumbled across my board.
I'm not one of those weirdos. I swear.
He actually saved me and my friends' lives a few times in high school.
-Cool.
-Yeah. yeah.
And ever since. I've just been trying to figure out who he is.
Not to unmask him to the world or anything. just to know. you know?
And to. hopefully. thank him face to face.
I actually created this app that monitors his sightings.
Wait. you created Spidey Tracker?
You heard of it? Nice.
Where is Spider-Man?
Little chat room right there.
Now. we know he's definitely from Queens.
Not the biggest revelation.
But I have been able to narrow it down to two prime suspects.
Roger Harrington
Science
Yeah. if you knew who they were.
it would really blow your mind.
I'm sure.
Ned. by the way.
I'm...
God. there's. like.
50 people in our apartment.
Statistically speaking. that means at least two of them are sociopaths...
which is kind of cool.
Nice flowers.
They're a housewarming gift.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Okay. Most people just brought beer and chips.
That's very nice.
I'm MJ.
I'm... I'm Maynard.
Maynard.
You two don't know each other?
No. I'm a neighbor.
Friendly neighbor.
Sorry
So. how was the interview?
I'm gonna go put these in water.
It was nice to meet you Maynard. Nerd.
Maynard. Yeah.
Excuse me.
Did you go? Please tell me that you went.
Yeah. No I went.
And?
And I got the job.
My God. MJ. that's amazing.
I turned it down.
What?
Yeah. I don't wanna work for some soulless corporation.
They're not all soulless.
Okay. They're all mostly soulless.
But don't you want. like. health insurance?
Yeah. of course I do. But at what cost?
Depends on your deductible.
You mean. like. your principles?
-Yes.
-Sorry.
I don't know. I know it sounds cheesy...
but something is just telling me...
that I'm supposed to be waiting for something great. you know?
Okay. Well. to waiting for something great.
To waiting for something great.
Well. the wait is over.
To your new home.
Dude. this is top-shelf.
Just like you.
I'm gonna hide this.
I lifted this off of him again.
But what if Ned needs the fire of a thousand sharks?
You mean heart palpitations?
-You can't save everyone.
-I can try.
That's my girl.
I'm sorry. I gotta...
When we get into MIT.
we should live together.
-Yeah. for sure.
-Yeah. I'd love that.
Be a fresh start. And we'll all be together.
Yeah. no. you're right. Yeah.
Fresh start.
You're gonna forget who I am.
Forget who you are?
What are you talking about?
It's okay. I'm gonna come and find you. and I'll explain everything.
-I love...
-Just wait.
Wait and tell me when you see me again.
My name is Peter Parker.
and I would like a coffee.
Is there anything else?
No.
Hey.
You think you don't have to listen to me now that you've got powers?
You know. this whole thing can get really scary.
You know that?
Well. yeah. it's already pretty scary.
Yeah.
And things can change.
like. very quickly...
in ways that we can't even imagine right now.
Believe me. I know.
I don't think you do know.
What do you mean?
God.
What?
I...
I live here. I just...
I'm gonna grab my stuff.
Is that my shirt?
No.
Cute dog.
Okay.
Hi. Peter. You have 107 new alerts.
Please check backlog.
What is happening?
The results of your body scan show a surge in the hormones...
associated with your arachnid DNA...
...resulting in the formation of organic web spinnerettes...
and dangerously heightened sensory receptors.
Okay. but I feel fine.
Prolonged isolation or emotional trauma could be contributing to this sudden change.
Have you experienced any recent traumatic events?
Peter?
I'm fine. E.V..
You don't seem fine.
I recommend you take some time to rebalance.
Well. that's not really an option. is it?
Mechanical web shooters and organic webs
cannot be used simultaneously.
Come on. Peter.
Alert. Senses are overloaded.
What the hell was that?
Your heightened senses are taking in too much information at once.
Okay. It's okay.
All right. organic webs. Peter Two had 'em.
He was cool. You're cool.
My God. that's hideous.
Okay. here we go.
Okay. that didn't work.
Organic webs. Come on! And bam!
No. no!
Stop!
What's going on. E.V.?
Shots fired at the Damage Control Data Center in Manhattan.
Suspect facial match with Scorpion.
Okay. I'm on my way.
Come on. Three. two...
Web! Stop!
Stop!
Web! Stop! Birds. birds. birds!
Web! Stop.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
God!
Web! Stop. stop. stop.
I don't know what you're looking for.
I'm looking for V-Max.
I don't know anything.
I'll see for myself.
God. God!
I'm sorry I'm late.
I've had a really crazy day.
Scorpion. do we really gotta keep doing this? My head is killing me.
You think I'm Scorpion?
Web!
What's happening to you?
You can't sense me anymore.
You.
What's going on with you. Spider-Man?
Warning. Arachnid hormones increasing.
Who are you?
Do you know who you are?
-We need some help over here.
-Yes. coming through.
Spider-Man.
What the hell?
Somebody get a medic.
DeWolff. is she hurt?
Is she okay?
-Is she okay?
-No!
-Just let me go...
-Don't! What is going on with you?
That wasn't Scorpion. okay.
I mean it was. but he was possessed by whatever hijacked that tank. okay.
-Look. please can I just...
-All right. listen. Slow down.
Listen. I don't know what this is.
but I need you to pull it together.
You almost killed a cop.
This isn't you.
I know. I'm sorry.
If you act like this again.
I cannot protect you.
Whatever this is. you need to fix it.
Through lattice chromodynamics...
we can arrange time and space in a grid.
Which allows us to simulate the quarks binding into the protons.
Cindy. is this a question about protons or more stuff about Avengers?
Okay. Guys. I love to tell stories...
but you know I gotta teach you some physics at some point here.
All right. Let it rip. Cindy.
Well. if Thanos was so worried about over-population...
why didn't he just use the magic glove to make more food?
Arthur. you wanna answer that question?
Hulk smash!
There you have it.
Excuse me. Dr. Banner. I...
-You okay?
-Yeah. sorry. it's just a headache.
Have you got a minute?
I wanted to talk to you about your inhibitor.
Sure. Don't worry. It's got failsafes.
I'm not gonna turn into the big green raging monster machine in the cafeteria.
But if you do see me with this thing off. run.
No. but. you're using target-specific short interfering RNA. right?
It's like gene silencing. you're just incorporating the gamma radiation?
What'd you say your name was?
Ned... Leeds.
So you found a way to suppress the expression of DNA...
even as it's undergoing the mutation due to gamma radiation. right?
-Yes.
-Okay. so. my question is...
would that same thing be possible with DNA that's mutating for another reason?
What's the reason?
I don't know.
Let's say that the host genome is mixed with some kind of foreign DNA.
Theoretically.
Theoretically? Yes. that's possible. Yes.
So. could you suppress only some parts of that DNA expression?
Like the bad aspects but just keep all of the good stuff?
You mean. like. if I wanted to keep some parts of Hulk but not others?
Right.
It would be enormously dangerous and complex. but...
if you were able to target the correct mRNA strand...
Possibly.
Wait. so you could just turn the mutating gene on and off...
as long as you do it before the mRNA transcription?
Maybe.
I mean. if you apply the same thinking.
you could even...
develop some kind of automatic inhibitor...
that would just adjust to any type of mutation.
Well. now you're talking about a universal inhibitor...
that would control anyone who has any powers.
It's a dangerous idea.
Well. yeah. But it's theoretical. right?
You're not one of my students. are ya?
No. I'm a grad student.
I've...
I've taken enough of your time.
I gotta get some books back to the library.
The library is that way.
Right. Right. Duh.
How would you decide?
What's that?
Well. what parts of nature are good or bad?
What if you're trying to control the expression...
of something that needs to be expressed?
Good luck with your studies. Ned.
Thank you. Professor.
Like reptiles...
- God.
- ...amphibians and arthropods...
...spiders shed skin
at key points in their life cycles.
The process is known as molting.
Fourth inhibitor prototype complete.
While molting is a natural...
-part of a spider's life cycle...
-Okay. come on. Come on.
...it can leave the spider vulnerable to threats.
Upload inhibitor beta build seven.
...process is initiated by hormonal changes...
Uploaded. Would you like to run a test?
Yeah. run it.
...few hours to several days.
Spiders have three stages in their life cycle.
Each stage is characterized by physical changes...
with the largest changes occurring during the beautiful transition to adulthood.
A LIFE IN WEBS: Journey through the life cycle of a spider
For those who make it through...
molting amounts to a kind of rebirth.
Can you turn that spider stuff off?
Turning off video.
-Inhibitor active.
-Okay. here we go.
Come on. Come on.
Keep an eye on my vitals.
Inhibitor engaged.
Suppressing arachnid hormones to your baseline levels.
Okay.
All right. E.V.. let's do this.
Initiating field test one.
That's working.
Alert. Inhibitor is overheating.
Functionality reducing.
INHIBITOR OVERHEATING
Yeah. I'm sensing that.
Alert. Senses are overloaded.
Senses are overloaded. Alert.
Web grenades activated.
GRENADES ACTIVATED
Oh sh...
Inhibitor field test one. failure.
Yo. Spider-Man. you okay?
Yeah. I'm just trying out some new tech.
Yeah. To get rid of that monster inside you?
Still can't sense me?
Guess your technology isn't working.
You know. you're the only person I've met that I can't...
hop into.
I'm sure that's really frustrating for you.
I'll get in there one day.
What do you want?
I wanna know why a half-human. half-spider would decide to work for an organization...
whose sworn mission is to hunt down anybody who's different.
Damage Control isn't after you because you're different.
They're hunting you down because you're dangerous.
Now. what do you want?
Since you're a very simple spider.
let me spell it out for you.
Damage Control has something that I need.
You mean V-Max?
I was planning to use Scorpion to get it.
but you keep getting in my way.
I will always be in your way.
You sure about that. Peter Parker?
You know. your apartment is kinda like a parody...
of where you think a sad single guy in his 20s might live.
Take-out containers.
free weights. protein powder.
You're bluffing.
You know.
you're not hard to track down. Peter.
Well. at least not for someone like me.
I did find one interesting thing. though.
In of all places...
coffee cup.
E.V.. display home work station.
You spent four years erasing Peter Parker from existence?
No wonder the spider's trying to swallow up the man.
I wonder if MJ would even recognize you.
I think I might go see how she's doing.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
No. her roommate was nice enough to post a new address online.
How about this? I'll race you there.
If you touch her...
Better start swinging.
I'm fast.
Hey.
It's a long way to MJ's.
You better pick up the pace.
E.V.. track physical anomalies.
Searching for physical anomalies between subjects.
Please stand by.
Thank you all so much for coming today.
I'm sorry about that.
Give it up for Spider-Man...
In a race for the love of his life.
and it's not looking good.
Come on. Spidey. Keep up.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Spider-Man!
E.V.. run these numbers with the others.
Analyzing jump distances for patterns.
Get me that jump data.
Calculating.
Come on. I need an answer!
Calculations complete.
You have a limit to your jump radius. don't ya?
Thirty-three feet.
I don't see anybody up here for you to hop into.
Very clever.
Like I said. you're not getting near her.
-Hey. hey. hey.
-MJ! I'm sorry. but you're in danger.
-Where's your roommate?
-What?
Where's Ned?
In Boston with friends. Why?
Okay. good. You gotta come with me.
What? I don't know if you're the real Spider-Man.
-I'm not coming with you.
-We don't have time for this.
-Please. Come on.
-You need to get out of my apartment.
Look. this is gonna sound insane...
but there is someone who is after you who is really dangerous. okay?
And I promised you
that I would keep you safe.
Please. you just have to trust me. Come on.
Fine.
Web. Stop.
Web stop.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah. yeah. I'm fine.
Okay. We should be safe up here.
Okay. well. safe from what?
I'm not entirely sure.
Okay. well. what do they want with me?
-I don't know.
-You don't know?
It doesn't make any sense.
Why would they choose me?
I wish I could tell you. I just...
We knew each other. didn't we?
What?
It's the only explanation.
It's been driving me crazy for years...
all the times that Spider-Man saved either me or Ned.
It was the Washington Monument...
and then it was London and Prague and the Night Monkey.
I mean. twice is a coincidence.
but over and over again...
We knew each other. Tell me I'm wrong.
Well. you're wrong.
What were we?
Were we classmates or friends or something?
Look. I don't know what you're talking about.
Were we something more?
I just. I can't. I can't remember.
And I feel like someone scrambled my brain.
And you're the only one who would know why.
This is crazy. I can't...
I know that you can't tell me the truth.
But I need to know.
Maybe there's a part of me that still remembers.
Peter.
MJ.
Hey. Peter.
I've missed you so much.
I can't believe you figured it out.
I did.
Go ahead. Peter. Touch her.
Hold her.
You've been wanting to for so long.
True love's kiss breaks the spell...
and reunites the star-crossed lovers.
MJ would vomit.
You really are a simple spider. aren't you?
I see why you like her.
She's...
she's smart...
funny...
and a little dark and twisted.
I mean. it is sad.
There is. like. no thoughts of you in here...
whatsoever.
But you knew that. didn't you?
You're a monster.
If you loved someone the way that I love her...
then you'd know that
what you're doing right now is unforgivable.
Is that so?
You know. some people would kill to hold the person they love one last time.
Stop it now.
You're running out of time. Peter.
Soon enough. it won't just be your friends who don't remember Peter Parker.
Maybe you should write a letter to yourself.
Get out of her.
Who's the monster now. Peter?
MJ.
MJ. No. no. no. God.
God. please. no. come on.
Come on. come on. come on.
Thank God. Thank God.
You're okay. You're okay.
I'm so sorry.
Stop. Wait. wait. stop. stop.
please. I'll quit.
You win. you win. you win.
Just don't hurt her.
You're a mess. Spider-Man.
Anytime I want...
I can be anyone I want.
So you can't protect MJ...
even from herself.
It really is a nice letter.
Little heavy-handed.
But not bad.
SCANNING COMPLETE
You're okay.
I'm gonna take you someplace safe.
What?
Take me to 3165...
Lafayette Street.
Navigating to Empire State University.
Wait. wait. wait! Okay.
-I got you. I got you.
-Are you sure?
-Yep.
-Okay.
Cause I feel like
I'm slipping a little bit.
-You're not slipping.
-Okay.
You're okay. you're okay. you're okay.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. I'm fine. I'm fine.
Okay.
Can we just slow down...
-for like two seconds. please?
-Well. we're almost there.
Yeah. yeah. but you just told me I was mind controlled.
Well. not technically.
I mean. you're lucky
I believe in that stuff. okay?
Because governments have been doing it for years. especially the French.
-Are you okay?
-Yeah...
Look. Sorry. I'm just trying to take you someplace safe. okay?
I don't feel safe.
Shit.
- Sorry.
- Watch out!
You're losing it. kid.
Thought you'd be able to see that coming a mile away.
What is wrong with you?
-You could've killed us.
-Excuse me.
You show up to my house unannounced. what do you think's gonna happen?
Wait. this is your house?
-No. no. Don't. don't. don't.
-Who the hell is that?
Who the hell are you?
She's...
You know.
No. I don't know.
That's why I just asked you.
She's in danger. Frank.
Look. I need your help. okay?
-Yeah. looks like it.
-Well. come on. You owe me.
-For... Aren't you sick of this story?
-Staten Island!
Nah. Staten Island.
What more do you want me to do?
I literally saved your life.
You're out of your mind. kid!
What. I gotta save it twice...
-to get a favor out of you?
-That guy couldn't hit me...
-with a handful of rice.
-I mean. what does that sound like to you?
-I had him exactly where I want him.
-A drug dealer was gonna shoot a guy...
-I'm seein' him right there.
-...then I webbed the gun...
-...out of the drug dealer's hand...
-I know exactly what I'm...
-...completely up for.
-and then kicked that drug dealer...
-Okay. fine. go ahead.
-...back into a storage container.
-What would you call that?
-What does that sound like to you?
I don't care. I just wanna go home.
That's an excellent idea. Kick rocks.
-Go home.
-No. wait. wait. Frank. Frank. Frank. wait.
Please.
I have got to keep her safe. okay?
And I don't have anywhere else to go.
You like chili?
I made chili.
All right. Just...
watch out for the claymores.
Don't wanna pick up pieces of you for the next two weeks.
Hey. I definitely would not eat that chili.
So. you telling me that maniac...
behind all that tank nonsense is nothing but a goddamn teenager?
And it's not just the tank. it's every attack on Damage Control this past month.
And how does a kid learn how to drive a tank?
I don't know. Frank.
-Beat you all over the street like that.
-She did not beat me.
This your family?
Would you get the hell away from that?
Look. I got one rule in this house.
You don't touch anything.
You don't move anything.
You sure as shit don't ask me any goddamn questions about anything.
So. three rules.
I see why you like her.
I'm gonna go put some pants on.
Don't touch the chili.
I like him.
Of course you do.
So I managed to pull this image from my
HUD and run it through the system.
Who is she?
Until a couple months ago. nobody.
She was in and out of foster care.
psych hospitals. and then eventually she
ran away and dropped off the grid.
There's hardly any information about her
that hasn't been scrubbed.
But she's classified as a telepath.
And now we have a name.
Jean Grey.
Yeah. These are the Damage Control sites that she hasn't hit yet...
so if she surfaces...
then my facial tracking program will pick her up.
Right.
Yeah? What then?
Well. don't worry about "what then."
Just look after her.
Don't worry about it?
I'm just supposed to sit here and babysit your girlfriend?
-I don't need to be babysat. so yeah.
-She's not my girlfriend.
All right. all right.
Look. what's the plan?
Just gonna hope that your facial tracking program works?
And you get yourself killed.
I gotta watch her the rest of my life?
I'm not gonna get killed. Frank.
I can catch her. okay?
I just...
I just have to fix my inhibitor and then I'll be good to go.
Well. what do you need to do that?
Frank. You do not have what I need to do that. okay?
You know you've got some mouth on you.
What do you think.
you have an anti-static mat...
a tonal probe. and micro tools?
I got all that shit.
What for?
-Bombs.
-Bingo.
Unbelievable.
Hey. do you think it's safe to maybe call someone...
and let them know I'm okay?
Like your boyfriend?
No. Like my roommate.
I don't think that's such a good idea.
you know. because...
she already knows who he is.
and she can inhabit anyone she wants. so...
Right. Yeah.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. You're right.
-Sorry.
-No. it's fine. I totally get it.
If I called my boyfriend...
he'd just ask me a bunch of questions that I couldn't answer...
and then he'd tell me
I was being withholding again.
-Withholding?
-Yep.
Sounds like your boyfriend's kind of a jerk.
But why'd he think you're withholding?
I don't know. You tell me.
masked vigilante behind the curtain.
Okay. I see your point.
So what about you?
What about me?
Well. do you have a Mrs. Spider-Man?
Do I have a Mrs. Spider-Man?
No. No.
Why not?
Why not? Because I'm...
I'm too withholding. obviously.
Welcome to the club.
There was someone.
-Really?
-Yeah. yeah. yeah.
What happened?
I...
I had to let her go.
To keep her safe.
I'm sorry.
That must have been really hard for you.
Yeah. it was. Yeah. It is.
It is really hard.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah. yeah. I'm okay. I...
You know what. I'm just gonna come over.
Hold on. hold on. hold on.
What's going on?
It just keeps overheating on me.
It's been stumping me for days.
Before I switched to aerospace...
I was gonna major in biochemical engineering.
so. do you mind if I...
Yeah. for sure.
Here. There you go.
Wow.
So. does the device itself...
I mean. does it generate any kind of radiation or a magnetic field?
Cause that would definitely interfere.
Yeah. it has a micro magnetic field. but I accounted for that in the design.
Okay. well. what about your suit?
It actually dissipates into the fabric.
which is pretty cool.
Okay.
What about those?
What about what?
Your goggles. or whatever you call 'em.
They would create a field.
It would be tiny. but...
But it's on your head.
which is very close to the inhibitor.
Which is probably why it's overheating.
MJ. that is genius.
Okay. this has to work.
Inhibitor engaged.
Suppressing selected arachnid hormones.
Okay. That feels better.
That feels totally better.
My head feels so clear.
Web. web.
And I'm not shooting organic webs.
My God. MJ. that. like. totally worked.
You know. this is some really intense stuff you're working on here.
Well. yeah. it's really important.
Yeah. but this is like. I mean.
this is like altering your DNA.
I mean. this is the kind of stuff you put on.
like. I don't know. like a monster.
Well. if you've seen what's been happening to me over the last couple days...
then you might understand.
Yeah. well. I've been with you for the last few hours...
and that's not what I've seen.
And what have you seen?
From my side of the curtain?
A really good guy who might just be changing.
Well. I don't mean to overstep.
I'll let you get back to it.
Can't sleep either?
You want coffee?
Sure.
You get your shit fixed?
Yeah. I've been wearing it all night.
So far. so good.
I made this other one universal.
So if I could get it on Jean.
it should completely shut down her powers.
You know what else would work?
You just shoot her.
Nice.
Jesus Christ.
That has gotta be the goofiest shit I ever seen in my life.
What. you can't even take the mask off to drink a cup of coffee?
Don't take it personally. Frank.
It stays on for everybody.
Even her?
Who is she. kid?
I don't know.
That's horseshit. Who is she?
-I'm telling you. I don't know who she is.
-What are you doin'? You care about her.
-You're pretending not to. Why?
-I don't care about her.
Look. I don't know who she is. Frank. Okay?
I don't have anybody. I'm like you.
I just keep to myself.
You're like me?
What do you know about me. kid?
You think this is a choice?
Living like this. it's a lifestyle? Is that what you think?
Kid. this is a sentence.
You know somethin'...
If I had one second...
people I love were still breathing.
you think I'd be hiding behind a mask?
You think I'd pretend to be something that I'm not...
acting like a goddamn coward?
I got a facial match
She's at the Damage Control HQ in Manhattan.
I gotta go. Okay.
She's gonna be okay.
I'll see to it.
Thanks. Frank.
Hey.
You just gonna let him go by himself?
You know. I think he might need you.
Kinda like you needed him on Staten Island.
Yeah.
You can't hide from me forever. Bill.
You've got a strong door.
but it's the wall you have to worry about.
Who are you and what do you want?
I'm Jean Grey...
and you know what I want.
Jean?
You looked me up? I'm blushing.
I told you what would happen to your girl if you got in my way.
You're not getting near her again.
And you're definitely not getting inside that vault.
Maybe not.
But this guy might.
Jean. you don't know what you're dealing with.
You know. you and Banner have a lot in common.
Both fighting a losing battle against the monster that lives inside you.
Jean. this is the Hulk. you can't just...
What the hell?
I see.
Trying to muzzle me like you muzzle yourself?
I can't let you in there.
Whatever V-Max is. you're not getting it.
Like hell I'm not.
Crap.
Jean. don't do this.
Save your breath.
Frank. what are you doing here?
What you think I'm doing?
I'm saving you.
This is way above your pay grade. dude.
- We're fighting the Hulk.
- Shit!
Really?
Get out!
-Stop shooting him!
-Are you out of your goddamn mind?
He's... Banner's not the problem! She is.
I thought I told you to stay home and watch MJ.
Yeah. you did.
And then she tells me I gotta come watch you.
Wait. did she actually say that to you?
Are you blushing. daffodil?
I'm not blushing.
Goddamn it.
I knew I should have brought a bigger gun.
That's a good idea. "Bring a bigger gun.
What are you gonna do. tickle him to death?
No. Look. change of plan.
First we get this on the Hulk.
Then we go after Jean.
I got one better
That's the highest casualty-producing threat.
You contain it. I go find the source.
I take it down. You got it?
Are you just trying to get out of fighting the Hulk?
-I guess so.
-Okay. whatever. dude.
I got this.
-Wait. no. Frank. Frank. Frank.
-What?
Do not kill her!
Don't start with that soft serve bullshit.
You know something? I'm gonna do this. I'm gonna do it my way.
Just... just go. just go.
And don't get within 33 feet!
So frustrating.
Hey.
This guy's got issues.
No no.
No. not again. No.
Dr. Banner? Is that you?
Spider-Man. What happened?
Where am I?
-Hey. hey. hey.
-Did I do all this?
-You...
-Did I hurt anyone?
It's not your fault. She was in your mind.
You weren't in control.
-I lost my inhibitor.
-Look here. here.
It's the only thing keeping the monster inside.
It's okay. I got another one here.
I just need you to put this on.
-What is it?
-It's universal.
It should work on you.
Please. sir. there's people in the building.
Just put it on.
You okay?
My head. I think she broke something!
Is she still in there?
No.
It's the other guy.
Bruce? Look. I can get you out of here. okay?
I just need you to put that inhibitor on.
Get away from me!
He's coming.
I can't control.
Yes. you can. Bruce! Yes. you can!
Get out of the building!
Get everyone out of the...
No! No!
Banner. please. Look at me.
No Banner. No girl.
Only Hulk.
I didn't know you could get that big.
Good luck with that. Peter.
There you are.
Just hold still. Just hold still...
God.
No lethal rounds.
Tracking time to detonation.
Ninety seconds to detonation.
I know! I know!
Come on.
Why is your skin so thick?
Inhibitor cannot attach.
Come on!
Dr. Banner...
please.
Bruce.
It's Peter.
I'm your friend.
Bruce.
Throw down your guns.
or you'll get the next one in the head.
Where is she?
What did you...
It's over. Jean.
Sara.
Is that my gun?
Is anyone hurt? It's just me?
Is anyone hurt?
Spider-Man...
You saved my life.
And you saved God knows how many lives...
by making sure she didn't find what she was looking for in there.
Still inside. We got her coming through.
Before she passed out.
she tried to say something.
A name. Sara.
Does that mean something to you?
Before you got the inhibitor on her...
she managed to get in my mind for a moment.
Sara was the name of someone I worked closely with that recently passed.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Somehow the memory of Sara must have affected her.
Well. I'd love to talk to her when she wakes up. if that's all right.
Of course. She'll be transferred to our facility on Roosevelt Island.
Now. I'm just as eager to get her talking as you are...
but let's not strain her too much in one day.
Yeah. of course.
Thank you. Spider-Man.
My pleasure.
MJ!
It worked. She's in custody.
You're safe now.
You left this.
Did you want me to find it?
No. No.
Look. I can explain. I...
Can you take that off. please?
What?
The mask.
I think I deserve to have this conversation with "Peter Parker.
You came to the party at our apartment the other night.
And the donut shop.
The year I went off to school.
Why didn't you tell me then?
I was trying to protect you.
Yeah. well. I've almost been killed. like. five times in the past 24 hours...
so it's not really working that well.
I know. I'm sorry. I...
Were you ever gonna tell me?
Right.
So you just were gonna make that decision for me.
I know. I'm sorry.
I don't really need you to keep saying that you're sorry.
-I don't know what you want me to tell you.
-I want you to tell me...
why you would do this to me.
I lost someone.
And they'd still be here if it wasn't for me.
I didn't read you that letter because...
I didn't want anything like that to happen to you.
But that's not really your decision to make.
I know it's not. but...
You mean everything to me.
And I've been trying to live my life without you. but I...
I can't.
I love you.
This spell or whatever it is that you did...
It worked.
All these memories that you're saying that we have together. I don't...
I don't have them.
And I do see why. you know.
she would love you...
the girl you wrote that letter to. but...
I understand...
that you did what you had to do to protect her.
And for that I'm so grateful.
But I...
I don't love you.
Because I don't...
I don't even know you.
I should probably go now.
I really am sorry. Peter.
I don't have a phone.
Do you mind taking me home?
Yeah. of course.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Yeah. sure.
I'm going to...
Yeah. yeah. Yeah. of course.
Do you wanna come up?
Just to say hi to Ned. Maybe.
I would love that.
Okay.
The Hulk. a.k.a. Dr. Bruce Banner.
is in custody...
currently being transferred to a psychiatric ward.
So sad.
After years as a peaceful academic...
the question the world asked today is...
What finally snapped?
Hey. I'm nearby.
-Hey. I'm nearby.
-MJ?
-Yeah.
-Hey. I'm nearby.
Hey. I'm nearby.
You're not gonna believe this...
-Hey. I'm nearby.
-...but the Spidey Tracker app...
-...says that Spider-Man...
-Hey. I'm nearby.
-...is in the direct vicinity.
- Yeah? No way. That's crazy.
- Hey. I'm nearby.
Hey. I'm nearby.
Ned. Spider-Man. Spider-Man. Ned.
It's nice to meet you. Ned.
Hello.
-I'm not. like. a weirdo or anything. I'm...
-He's a little weird.
Why are you here?
-I...
-I was...
-I was on a subway platform.
-She was in the... Platform. Right.
-And she was on her phone.
-Yeah. and... Yeah. I got a little distracted.
-And the train was coming and he...
-I mean...
And I just swooped her right up.
-Yep. Saved me.
-Yeah.
My God.
Why has that never happened to me?
So what if you're mid-swing and you decide you need to pee?
Do you just land on top of a building?
What?
Do you drop down to ground level and run into a coffee shop and you're like...
Hey. it's Spider-Man. I need to pee"?
Or do you find a rooftop somewhere?
No. I don't find a rooftop somewhere. Ned.
Is this really what you wanna be asking him right now?
Yeah. dude. come on.
you can ask me anything.
You wanna know how my web shooters work?
I mean. I already know how the web shooters work.
Is that right?
Well. there's obviously some sort of a shear-thinning fluid...
that is cycling within a chamber. right? So it can keep its liquid form.
And then. when you activate it by pressing on the triggers...
it runs through a Teflon turbine...
and then it hardens when it interacts with the air. Right?
I mean. not exactly. but...
Okay. okay. well. then tell me what's in the web fluid.
I would guess something like a long chain polymer.
Nylon?
That's pretty close.
Okay. okay. What about Nomex or Kevlar?
All right. then. Keep your secrets.
If you're referring to the incident with the dragon...
I was barely involved.
All I did was simply give your uncle a little nudge out the door.
Solid reference.
Banh mi time.
You ordered banh mis?
I ordered five banh mis.
We have Spider-Man in the apartment.
He's gonna get fed.
Sorry about him. He's just. like. very excited that you're here.
You kidding? This is. like. the most fun I've had in years.
I really missed you guys.
You guys really do look like best friends.
What do you mean?
You should tell him.
He can handle it.
Yeah. I know.
When she was inhabiting you on the rooftop...
she kissed me...
and I kissed her back...
because I thought it was you.
but I didn't know.
And I'm really sorry.
I just thought you should know.
Thanks for telling me.
I mean. it's not like I remember anything anyway. so...
Really?
Yeah. It was weird. it was like.
one second I was sitting at my desk....
and the next second I was lying on the street.
I don't know. like a light switch went off.
What?
So you don't remember anything?
No. Why?
Metzger said he remembered thinking about someone named Sara...
but what you're saying is that you don't remember anything at all?
I mean. yeah. it was instantaneous.
That's what made it so scary.
He lied to me.
I heard you caught leshy.
Yeah. Her name's Jean Grey.
I need some help determining the size of some potatoes.
-Potatoes?
-I think that's Black Widow.
I think Metzger lied to me about a name.
Can you see if there's a connection between Jean and someone named Sara?
These potatoes sound meager.
Wow. That really is your office.
Well. well. well.
Internet. government records...
and a lot of data related to Jean Grey has been scrubbed by Damage Control.
Data about what?
Her sister.
Wait. Jean has a sister?
Sara Grey.
Also a telepath.
Damage Control took her into custody for study and observation.
Wow. I mean. you can probably guess what they mean by that.
Experimentation and other human rights violations.
Yes. exactly. Wait. who are you?
-Hi. Ned Leeds. Big fan.
-I'm...
Hi.
I'm sorry.
I'm just so happy that the sad man has friends.
Thanks. I owe you one.
Good luck. Spider-Man.
Bye.
She was just looking for her sister...
and I handed her to the people that took her.
-I gotta go.
-Hey. Peter...
Yeah?
Just be careful. all right?
Yeah. I will.
Spider-Man's name is Peter?
Jean. who do you want to be?
Her. Pink jacket.
She's too far.
You're gonna have to hop.
Hop?
First. pick someone close.
And then...
Each hop has a limit.
But you can string them together and go as far as you want.
And when you let go...
You're right back where you started.
Could you do that to everyone in this park at once?
Well. yeah. maybe one day.
If you get really good.
How could she just...
send us away?
She wasn't really a mom.
Not like that. anyway.
She was. before we changed.
Yeah. well. if that's all it takes for you to stop being a mom...
then you're not a mom.
What would you do if you had daughters like us?
I'd love them.
-Especially the redhead one.
-Shut up.
We have each other.
And we have ice cream.
-One mint chip. one chocolate?
-Yeah.
Okay.
Now I know how you're playing.
-Get down!
-Get down! Get down!
-Get down on the ground now!
-Down!
-Sara!
I'm sorry. Jean.
I have to keep you safe.
Subject is awake. Heart rate is 94 bpm.
Jean. that's not gonna work anymore. thanks to Spider-Man.
Jean?
I need you to breathe.
I need you to look at me and breathe.
Okay?
You're safe. Breathe.
Where is she?
Like your sister.
you've been blessed with a power...
that has the potential to do tremendous good in the world...
or tremendous damage.
A power like yours in the hands of a child is an impossible burden.
But imagine...
if that power was placed
in the hands of people...
who actually know what to do with it.
Where is my sister?
You're gonna change the world. Jean.
Hey!
Frank.
I know where you are. what you're doing.
Yeah? And how's that?
I got eyes everywhere. kid.
Look. Frank.
Damage Control kidnapped Jean's sister.
Jean was just trying to find her.
We were wrong about everything.
Sentimental horseshit.
You've seen what she can do and what she's capable of.
What. you're gonna let her loose? Is that what you're gonna do?
I'll tell you right now. you do that.
I handle it my way.
Frank. please. can you just...
Frank!
Distance check?
Forty-foot clearance.
Locking down the room.
Locking down.
Disengage inhibitor.
Jean. your powers are now fully operational.
As you can tell.
we are beyond your jump radius.
Tell me what V-Max is.
You're the second person to ask me about that.
WEBSITE - HDHUB4U.AG
I have no idea what that means.
She sent me a message.
She was trying to help me find her.
She communicated with you telepathically across all that distance?
We did register a huge spike in that session.
Fascinating
What does it mean?
I don't know.
Let's begin.
Our work with Sara centered on two areas...
identifying the source of her power...
and identifying a path towards copying it.
If we could find a way to record a telepathic brain during a jump...
then perhaps we could replicate those pathways...
in a mind of our choosing.
This instrument is your sister's legacy.
We built this together over many months of trial and error.
I hope you and I can honor her sacrifice.
What are you talking about?
Trigger the first jump.
Tell me what V-Max is.
I know that's where you're hiding her.
SCANNING
She's jumping.
Copy.
We're in full lockdown.
Process has commenced.
What process?
Hey. whoa.
that's a pretty serious look there. dude.
Hey. hey. whoa! What the hell. man?
Come on. I'm a friend of Damage Control. What are you doin'?
It's gonna be like that. You wanna go.
All right.
All right. well. just give me a sec.
Give me a sec.
I'm not in high school anymore.
Do you stretch? You a big stretcher?
I mean. you should do it in your line of work.
What about you? You guys stretch?
It's so good for you.
You ready?
Watch your head!
Where is Jean Grey?
That's jump 26.
Recordings look good.
Excuse me. sir.
We have an intruder.
You were right.
She's much stronger than her sister.
Increase the frequency.
You're doing very well. Jean.
SCANNING.
Jean?
Jean. can you hear me?
You're a murderer.
Her frequencies are evolving.
This doesn't make sense.
The last thing my sister saw was this room.
Her brainwaves are somehow affecting the objects around her.
Shut it down.
I'm trying. sir.
What do you mean you're trying?
The last thing my sister saw was this goddamn room!
-Shut it down!
-I can't. sir.
Move.
I can't let you do that. Bill.
The only hands that will wield this power...
are mine.
-What...
-What do you want?
Jean. I'm here to help you.
You put me here.
I know. and I'm sorry about Sara.
and I'm sorry that I got it so wrong.
If you came here...
to save a helpless girl from Damage Control.
you're too late.
They're the ones who need saving.
And now...
so do you.
Here we go.
God. that's cool.
Jean! Jean. please!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
What?
Isn't it funny...
how your friends from Damage Control developed a special weapon...
just for you?
They've got a whole task force ready.
Just in case you ever get out of line.
People are monsters.
You shouldn't trust them any more than they trust you.
I'm a little busy. Frank.
We got a problem. kid.
She got ahold of everyone within a kilometer of the island.
Wait. what?
Hey. look. if you're gonna do something. you better do it now.
I'm trying!
Kid?
Shit! Goddamn it.
My sister died...
in this room...
surrounded by these men.
And her only crime...
was that she was special.
Just like you.
Just like me.
People like us don't get to live a normal life.
We don't get to have friends or a family.
Those people are gone.
That life is over.
So why don't you just be honest with yourself?
Are you Peter Parker?
Or are you Spider-Man?
I'm both.
Jean. please.
This won't make it right.
Come on. You're not a killer. Jean.
You have no idea what I am.
I know that you loved your sister.
And I know that losing her felt like you'd lost everything.
If you come any closer. he dies! They all do!
You know this won't bring her back. right. Jean?
You...
Don't be so sure I can't get into your mind.
I'm a lot more powerful since I last tried.
Go ahead.
Hey.
You think you don't have to listen to me now that you've got powers?
You know. this whole thing can get really scary.
You know that?
It's already pretty scary.
Yeah.
And things can change. like. very quickly...
in ways that we can't even imagine right now.
I know.
No.
I don't think you do know.
What do you mean?
You're a really special person.
And I would hope that that will always make you feel really great about yourself...
but I know sometimes it doesn't.
Sometimes you'll be really lonely.
And sometimes...
because you're special...
people can do dark. monstrous things to you.
But...
this is what I want you to know.
You're beautiful...
and the people who love you...
we love you not because you're special.
we love you because you're you.
I want you to remember that.
Even when it feels like you're totally alone.
That's your deepest responsibility.
Never forget that.
no matter how powerful you become.
Hey.
I'm sorry about your sister.
I'm sorry about your aunt.
Yeah. you would've loved her.
Just because we've lost someone...
It doesn't mean we have to do this alone.
I mean. we can't.
Trust me. I've been trying.
It doesn't work.
Even if that's true...
I have no one.
You have me.
Are you hurt?
No. I'm fine.
I'm okay.
-Peter.
-I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
Peter. No.
Peter. Peter. No. no.
No. no. no. Peter. Peter.
Jean. you gotta get outta here.
They'll be looking for you.
No. no. no. Please. just stay with me.
Come on. hold on. Come on. please!
Jean. you're...
You're gonna be okay.
Just go.
Look at me.
Shock today. as Spider-Man arrived at Bellevue Hospital with a bullet wound
seemingly at death's door.
The reclusive crime fighter is in critical condition
as the city's top medical experts work to save him.
Tonight. all eyes are on Spider-Man.
The hero who saved New York so many times
is now in the hands of its best and brightest.
And the people of New York hold their breath.
Frank?
Where am I?
-No. no. no. Hey.
-Where's my mask?
Don't worry about that. I got you covered.
Hey. you're good.
Where's Jean? Is she okay?
Yeah. she's okay. She's okay.
-Where is she?
-Kid.
I think maybe she just left.
She was using her magic voodoo shit to keep you alive.
Yeah... she's all right.
I'm sorry.
-Frank. Frank. it's okay.
-Just... I'm really sorry for what I did.
-No. Frank. it's okay.
-And it's. no. it's a lot of things...
but it sure as shit ain't okay. all right?
I've seen...
I've seen real bravery. kid. in my day.
But that...
that was something else.
You crying. Frank?
No. I ain't...
You know. you look the exact way I thought you would.
You know.
A nice kid.
Never had a friend like that.
Are we friends now?
I can't believe I just saw you cry.
I didn't cry. What are you talking about?
Bullshit.
Yeah. this.
They've been doing it all night.
They've been here since you walked in.
Just take a look.
Yo. kid. when you came in.
they had to cut through the suit...
but when you're ready to split...
I got a plan
Dr. Moseley. 2495.
Hey. it's Spider-Man!
Spider-Man!
Hey!
Yeah. Spider-Man!
You're the best. Spider-Man!
Spider-Man!
Over here!
We love you!
Spider-Man! Spider-Man! Spider-Man!
I've...
Been thinking a lot about what you said.
And you'd be happy to know that I've decided I'm not...
I'm not gonna do this alone anymore.
I miss you. May.
I mean. I've still got a little pain in my back...
but I could probably get back out there if you need me for anything.
What I need you to do is rest.
I know. I know. but come on.
you gotta give me something.
I mean. how's the investigation going?
Well. Metzger's still missing. but...
your friend. Black Widow...
she's been helping us dig through all the records...
Damage Control tried to have scrubbed.
Had me drop by her office the other day.
And how was that?
Well. my skin feels amazing.
Attention. all units.
We have a confirmed bank robbery in progress.
Hey. are you getting this?
Yeah. I'm on it.
Hey. it's not that far from me.
I could probably meet you down there.
No. We can handle a robbery.
Just try to take care of yourself.
Okay.
You too.
Say hello to EJ and Marley for me.
Okay.
Spider-Man says hello.
Hi.
Hey.
Flower guy. right from the party?
I'm Peter.
Okay. Hello.
Peter
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-